Hi again! I'm in Sindelfingen at Stuttgart at the Off-Scene Fair and I'll take you with me.
Is that right? Yes, it fits.
The shape is quite chic.
It's so close to the bottom.
It makes a very elegant neck.
It's also nice, it makes you slim.
It's not so bad.
Exactly.
I'm now at Benno von Stein's stand.
I'm standing here and I'm going to slip something in here too.
Let's see what I can do to try it on.
I also have to say that this line runs because it has no side seams.
Yes.
I put the seams where they are most visually pleasing.
That's right, yes.
And take it out.
It's a feeling.
It's glittering, it's just glittering so much.
It's like a puff shoulder.
Is it a part that you can wear in the combination?
Yes.
Or do you take it out a little?
I'm here at the stand of Schnittmuskel, a label from Karlsruhe and I'm running with them today at the fashion show.
That was a bit of the initial intention to come here and then I thought I could also make a video.
Should I comment it as a make-up tutorial?
How do I make up a black dot?
We are now just after the show.
This was the great show crew of the Schnittmuskel show.
We all have our black post-apocalyptic point.
We had a lot of fun and now we're going to take a few more pictures.
I got the dress recommended to try on and I'll do that now and see how it looks.
I like the way it looks.
Super cute with the paint and the little lacing.
I like it very much and especially easy to pull out.
It makes a really nice figure. It fits really well.
But I also like the tips up here. Makes the distance here nice too.
Also the color and the pattern is very cool.
It's so warm with all the people and the outfits, but it's fun.
I'm here at Chronomatic, a latex label from Berlin.
They make really great latex underwear.
I just like the colors.
It's not all black.
I can't reach it.
Gothic outfit. I just got a lot of tips in my hand.
I'll try it on now and see if it suits me at all.
I'm dressed up by the Wonderland 13 shop from Ulm.
A total goth outfit, contrast to before.
Including a cute arm-wrap with a bat and chain that is very nice.
The dress is also totally with pointed sleeves and I think I would actually put on a belt
or something so that it makes a little more style, but otherwise I think the outfit is
super clean and it's like the GOF high three outfit. Okay, that was it here from the OPSI fair in
Sindelfingen. I had a long day, my feet hurt, so I put them up now.
I hope you could come along a little bit here at the fair.
I'm now doing a party evening, stay here on the coach and I wish you a nice day.